[{"answer": "We didn't even really have it.  I happen to know for a fact that the only Stevie Wonder single we have is", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh, so what's the point then", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I know what they're worth.  Give me fifty and get them out", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I must have nothing.  Their my husband's", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Look.  Can I pay you properly?  You don't have to tell him what you got. Send him fort", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Look... I... I'm sorry.  I don't want to be any part of this", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " my friend import.  my friend. Break beats.  my friend. my friend, my friend... What's going on here?  Are you guys stealing for other people now", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh really.  You two are slamming to my friend now", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Shit", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well, I liked you.  You were a deejay, and I thought you were hot, and I didn't have a boyfriend, and I wanted one", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah, sure.  More so then than I am now.  That's life though, isn't it", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What were the others", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What's the obvious stuff", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Oh, my friend, shut up", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "-- I don't fucking know what chance you fucking have", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Just ask it", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Is what better?  Better than what", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Is it better", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well.  Sex, I guess.  Is sex with him better", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well.  Sex, I guess.  Is sex with him better", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Of course it is", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You really think it would make a difference either way", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Well the answer is that I don't know either.  We haven't done it yet", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "But not even before, when he was living upstairs", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " The sleeping together is better but not the sex because you haven't done it was him yet", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Exactly!  Fucking e", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Nor have you", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Oh no, my friend, that's not obvious enough. Not at all.  my friend, did you hear that", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Ooh!  A kind of recent record!  my friend's sly declaration of new classi", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I'll look for 'em.  How you doing", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Fine, I'm sure it's in the file at home.  I'll call you when I find it, and then we'll talk", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I guess", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I want you to say that you haven't, and I want it to be the truth", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I don't want to.  Don't need to.  I love you", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No... not really... I mean, I think about it... but no, I don't really think about it", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yeah, I'm fine.  I'm off the phone", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I'm upset, but I'm fine", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Good.  Great.  Yeah... Wow.  my friend.  Seems like a 100 million years ago now", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Fantastic but I'm a little busy right now.  Listen.  Do you want to come to dinner Saturday?  I'm having some friends over and I need a spare man. Are you a spare man", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What the fuck is that", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What band", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "My band", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "The band that found me and asked me to join", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I didn't make up the name.  It's the Steely my friend song.  And it was in The Commitments", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "They were fucking called that before I was in it, okay?  It wasn't my idea", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Don't forget your CDs", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Sure they are", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I got it.  You like Sting but you don't like my friend, because you've never heard of him", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I guess I am", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Don't worry about it.  Just get into bed.  Worry about that when you're better", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Who the fuck's Pig", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Okay, okay", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "-- It was my friend, you fucking idiot", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Because it's in The Big Chill", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Liar.  We saw it in the my friend doubl", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "So the minister says nice things, and then, what, we all troop outside and they bury him", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You're kidding.  A crematorium? my friend", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "Sure, I understand.  Look, I don't want to take up any more of your time.  You get back, and I'll wait here for a bus", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "What do you want to do", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Want to know what, exactly", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "It was like sex.  What else could it be like", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "What it was like", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Was it like good sex or was it like bad sex", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Was it like good sex or was it like bad sex", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "You know the difference", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "You know the difference", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Okay, that's cool, okay.  But the nice time we just had... was it nicer, as nice, or less nice than the nice times you were having a couple of weeks ago", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Oh, c'mon, my friend.  Just say something. Lie, if you want.  It'd stop me asking you questions and it'd make me feel better", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Well why the fuck would you want to lie, anyway", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Money does not matter.  I do not care how much you earn.  I'd just like you to be a little happier in your work, but beyond that you can do what you like", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "How?  How were we the same people", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "I had that idea when I was living with my friend and it was such a good idea that I was annoyed we weren't together anymore.  It might even be why I came back", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "What do you ever do that can't be cancelled", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "You had no right.  Supposing I was doing something that couldn't be cancelled", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "That's not the point.  I mean, what if the single isn't done in time", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Right.  Okay, then.  Shall we go", "docId": "High-Fidelity.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 78}]